rignite.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy | @RigniteInc

[HEADING heading=”h1″ highlight_words=”Policy” color=”orange”]Privacy Policy[/HEADING]

This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into the Rignite [Terms of Use](http://www.rignite.com/terms-of-use/ "Terms of Use"), available at http://www.rignite.com/terms. The term “ **Rignite** ,” “ **we** ,” and “ **us** ” includes Rignite and our affiliates and subsidiaries. The Privacy Policy explains how Rignite may:

  * collect,
  * use, and
  * disclose

information we obtain through the Rignite Service.

**“Personal Information”** means information that alone or when in combination with other information may be used to readily identify, contact, or locate you, such as: name, address, email address, or phone number. We do not consider Personal Information to include information that has been anonymized so that it does not allow a third party to easily identify a specific individual.

**THE RIGNITE SERVICE COLLECTS YOUR INFORMATION**

We collect Personal Information when:

  * you register to use the Rignite Service;
  * you connect your social network account with your Rignite account;
  * you post information about your customers to the Rignite Service;
  * you request information or customer service from us; and
  * you communicate with us.

We also collect information, such as anonymous usage statistics, by using cookies, server logs, and other similar technology as you use the Rignite Service.

**Registration.** To create an account, you may need to provide Personal Information, such as your name, username, password, email address, telephone number. You may also provide other optional information, including a business name and website url.

**Social Networks.** When you connect your social network account to the Rignite Service, we collect information from the social network. For example, we may collect the Personal Information you have made publicly available in Facebook, such as your name and profile picture or logo. With your permission, we may also collect other information to provide the functionality of the Rignite Service, such as your friend or connection list, any “likes,” “check-ins,” comments, or posting made by your friends or connections to your profile page or account, how often content is posted, the date of postings.

**Information You Post to the Rignite Service.** You may post information about your customers to the Rignite Service, which may include Personal Information.

**Customer Support.** We may collect Personal Information through your communications with our customer-support, marketing, and sales teams.

**Making Payments.** When you make payments through the Rignite Service, you may need to provide Personal Information to our third-party service providers, such as your credit card number. We do not collect any of the Personal Information you provide to make a payment, but we may collect information about the payment, such as the date and amount of the payment.

**Cookies, Automatic Data Collection, and Related Technologies.** The Rignite Service collects and stores information that is generated automatically as you use it, including your preferences and anonymous usage statistics.

When you visit the Rignite Service, we and our third-party service providers receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, and from cookies and similar technology. Cookies are small text files placed in visitors’ computer browsers to store their preferences. Most browsers allow you to block and delete cookies. However, if you do that, the Rignite Service may not work properly.

We, and our third-party service providers, may also use web beacons, pixels, and similar technology to collect anonymous information that helps us audit the success of content delivery, such as how many people open the emails we send and what other actions recipients take with our emails.

By using the Rignite Service, you are authorizing us to gather, parse, and retain data related to the provision of the Rignite Service.

**HOW RIGNITE USES YOUR INFORMATION**

We use Personal Information to:

  * facilitate and improve the Rignite Service; and
  * communicate with you.

We do not rent, sell, or share Personal Information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes.

We may use aggregate information for any purpose, including for marketing purposes.

**Internal and Service-Related Usage.** We use information, including Personal Information, for internal and service-related purposes only and may provide it to third parties to allow us to facilitate the Rignite Service. We may use and retain any data we collect to provide and improve our services.

**Communications.** We may send email to the email address you provide to us to verify your account and for informational and operational purposes, such as account management, customer service, or system maintenance.

**Marketing.** We do not rent, sell, or share Personal Information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes. We may use your Personal Information to facilitate transmittal of information that may be useful, relevant, valuable or otherwise of interest to you.

**Aggregate Data.** We may anonymize and aggregate data collected through the Rignite Service and use it for any purpose.

**RIGNITE MAY DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION**

We may share your information:

  * with our third-party service providers;
  * with social network websites, at your direction;
  * to comply with legal obligations;
  * to protect and defend our rights and property; and

with your permission.

**We Use Vendors and Service Providers.** We may share any information we receive with vendors and service providers retained in connection with the provision of the Rignite Service.

**Social Networking and Other Websites.** The Rignite Service may allow you to share your information with social networking websites. We do not share your information with them unless you direct the Rignite Service to share it. Their use of the information will be governed by their privacy policies, and we do not control their use of the shared data.

**As Required By Law and Similar Disclosures.** We may access, preserve, and disclose your Personal Information, other account information, and content if we believe doing so is required by law or if those actions are reasonably necessary to:

  * comply with legal process, such as a court order or subpoena;
  * enforce this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use;
  * respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third parties;
  * respond to your requests for customer service;
  * respond to law enforcement;
  * investigate and prevent unauthorized transactions or other illegal activities; or
  * protect our or others’ rights, property, or personal safety.

**Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers.** If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, financing due diligence, reorganization, bankruptcy, receivership, sale of company assets, or transition of service to another provider, your information may be sold or transferred as part of such a transaction. Any entity receiving such information may choose to treat such information according to its privacy policy and not the terms of this Privacy Policy.

_We may also disclose your Personal Information with your permission._

**SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us. We do not accept liability for unintentional disclosure.

By using the Rignite Service or providing Personal Information to us, you agree that we may communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the Rignite Service. If we learn of a security system’s breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically by posting a notice on the Rignite Service or sending an email to you. You may have a legal right to receive this notice in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice), please notify us at [support@rignite.com](mailto:support@rignite.com).

**INTERNATIONAL USERS**

By using the Rignite Service, you will transfer data to the United States.

By choosing to visit the Rignite Service or otherwise provide information to us, you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy will be governed by the law of the state of California and the adjudication of any disputes arising in connection with Rignites or the Rignite Service will be in accordance with the Terms of Use.

If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use, please note that you are agreeing to the transfer of your information to the United States and processing globally. By providing your information you consent to any transfer and processing in accordance with this Policy.

**UPDATE YOUR INFORMATION OR POSE A QUESTION OR SUGGESTION**

If you would like to update or correct any information that you have provided to us through your use of the Rignite Service or otherwise, or if you have suggestions for improving this Privacy Policy, please send an email to [support@rignite.com](mailto:support@rignite.com).

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY AND PRACTICES**

We may revise this Privacy Policy, so review it periodically. Before we broaden our use of Personal Information beyond what is stated in this Privacy Policy, we will make reasonable efforts to provide notice and obtain consent as required by law.

Posting of Revised Privacy Policy. We will post any adjustments to the Privacy Policy on this web page, and the revised version will be effective when it is posted.If you are concerned about how your information is used, bookmark this page and read this Privacy Policy periodically.

New Uses of Personal Information. From time to time, we may desire to use Personal Information for uses not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy. If our practices change regarding previously collected Personal Information in a way that would be materially less restrictive than stated in the version of this Privacy Policy in effect at the time we collected the information, we will make reasonable efforts to provide notice and obtain consent to any such uses as may be required by law.

**Contact Information**

Rignite  
444 Castro Street, Suite 710  
Mountain View, CA 94041  
Email: [support@rignite.com](mailto:support@rignite.com)

**Last Updated: August 1, 2012**
